剧情回顾...
-祝你好运  -你也是
-Good luck.  -Same to you.
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对：扣扣
后期：xyz 双语制作：冰小赐  雯雯  七色九天
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
-我们得发射闪光弹  -这毫无道理...
-We have to fire the flare.  -It doesn't make...
听着  你到底是把枪给我
Look, are you gonna give me the damn gun,
还是逼我去抢?
or am I gonna have to take it?
我的天啊
Please, God!
回来了  回来了
It's coming back! It's coming back!
我们得把那个男孩带走
We're gonna have to take the boy.
什么?  你说什么?
What? What did you say?
那个男孩  我们得带走他
The boy. We're gonna have to take him.
嘿  爸爸
Hey! Hey! What...Dad!
-爸爸  -不
-Dad!  -No!
爸爸  救我
Dad! Help me!
-Walt  -救我  爸爸
-Walt!  -Help me, Dad!
不  不  不
No, no, no...
停下
Stop it!
停下  我们不能这么做
Stop it! We can't!
Locke发现了一个...
Locke found a...
在地下发现了一个舱门
a hatch in the ground.
太阳在3小时内就会升起
The sun comes up in three hours
我们一定会在这里看见那一刻的
and we're all gonna see that happen.
我们大家今晚一起呆在这儿  好么?
We're gonna stay here tonight, OK?Together.
-John  你在干什么?  -我要下去
-John, what are you doing?  -I'm going in.
不管你反不反对  Locke还是准备下到那里面去
Locke's going into that thing,whether you like it or not.
我要下到舱门里去
I'm going to the hatch.
一起生  单独死  对么?
Live together, die alone, right?
是的
Right.
John  我想下面好像有东西
John! I think there's something down here!
爸爸  救我  爸爸
Dad, please! Dad!
Walt  Walt
Walt
Mike
Sawyer
Walt
Mike
坚持住  Mike
Hang on, Mike!
坚持住
Hang on!
Mike
Kate
迷 失
第二季 第二集
-Walt在哪儿?  -我不知道
-Where's Walt?  -I don't know.
-他在哪儿?  -我不知道
-Where is he?  -I don't know!
我儿子到底在哪儿?
Where the hell is my son?
Walt
你怎么伤到腿的?
How'd you hurt your leg?
被一辆车撞了
Got hit by a car.
恩
Yeah.
那么这是你前妻发来的文件
So, this is the paperwork your ex-wife sent over...
她不是我的前妻  她是...
She's not my ex-wife, man.
她只是Walt的母亲
She's just Walt's mother.
她  呃...
She...
Susan...她刚刚和她的男朋友在罗马找到工作
Susan, she just got a job in Rome with her boyfriend.
他们想让Walt跟他们在一起
They want to take Walt with them.
别担心  我会尽力帮助你的  Dylan先生
Don't worry, I'm gonna take real good care of you, Mr Dylan.
是Dawson
Dawson.
哦  是的  对不起  Dawson
Right. Sorry. Dawson.
那么她的男朋友...是叫Brian Porter么?
So this boyfriend,this is this guy Brian Porter?
是的  怎么了?  上面写了什么?
Yeah. Why? What's it say?
看起来好像Susan
It seems that Susan
想让你放弃作为Walt的父亲的权力
wants you to relinquish your rights as Walt's father
这样Porter先生就能领养他了
so that Mr Porter can adopt him.
她想让我放弃孩子?
She wants me to sign my son away?
是的  这是他们想领养你的孩子的唯一途径
It's the only way they can proceed with the adoption, yeah.
听着  如果你签了这个文件  从法律上来说
Listen, if you sign this document, legally
他对你来说就和在街上遇到的其它孩子没什么区别了
he'll be no different than any other kid you pass on the street.
你等于放弃了你所有作为父亲的权力
You'd be giving up your paternal rights.All of them.
那么我能阻止她离开么?
So then, can I stop her from going?
我想我们能申请一个禁令
Well,I guess we could file an injunction
那么她就不能离开这座城市了 但是...
so she couldn't leave the city,but...
对  好的
Yeah, that. That.
我就要那么做
I want to do that.
好的
Right.
Dawson先生
Mr Dawson,
你这么辛苦得赶来让我知道了
the fact that you came in through these doors tells me something.
我是你能负担得起的最好的律师
It tells me that I'm the best that you can afford.
如果我们继续这件事的话
If we go forward with this,
那么就会很耗钱...很多很多钱
it's gonna take money a... lot of it.
即使是在我这样的价位上
Even at my rates.
现在我们处在弱势  所以我得问你
This is David and Goliath,so I gotta ask you,
你真得想要这么做么?
are you sure you wanna do this?
他们不能带走我的儿子
They're not taking my son away.
Walt
Mike  你省点力吧
Mike! You should save your energy.
他们带走了我的儿子
They took my son!
是的  我看见了...上了一艘船
Yeah, I saw. Onto a boat,
这就意味着任你怎么叫他也听不到
which means he's not in shouting distance!
-你不会知道的  -我能感知到
-You don't know that!  -I got a good sense.
并且即使他听见了  你又能怎么办呢?
Even if he was,there's nothing you can do.
听着  如果他能听见我叫
If he can hear me,
他就知道我还活着
he knows I'm alive,
而且我一定会去找他
that I'm coming for him,
并且把他救回来
that I'm going to get him back!
现在我唯一的希望就是他能听见我喊他
Right now, all I got is that maybe my son can hear me...
这和你有关系么?
Does that make any sense to you?
Walt
Kate
John
放松  没事  没事的
Easy, easy, easy.
你后面
Behind you.
你是他么?
Are you him?
Jin
我们省点力吧
I thought we had to save our energy.
噢  呃...Jin还在水中
Yeah, well,Jin's still out there in the water,
如果不影响你  我打算再叫一会儿
so if it's OK by you I'm gonna keep shoutin' awhile.
Jin
心虚了么?
Feeling guilty?
什么?
What?
是你叫我发射闪光弹的
You made me fire that flare.
是我叫你发射...
I made you fire...
什么  这是我的错么?
What, this is my fault?
他们带走了我的儿子
They took my son.
他们找到了我们  带走了Walt
They found us, took Walt,
全都是因为你叫我发射了闪光弹
because you made me fire the flare.
至少Walt还在一艘船上
Well, at least Walt is on a boat.
可能还裹着毯子喝着可可
Probably wrapped in a blanket with a cup of cocoa
-而我们只是在...  -离开我的筏子
-while we're on...  -Get off my raft.
-什么?  -离...
-What?  -Get...
那是什么鬼东西?
What the hell was that?
你还紧握着你最好的伙伴啊
I see you managed to hold on to your best friend, there.
它不会有用了
Thing ain't gonna work anyway.
-它会有用的  -你落过水
-It'll work.  -You were underwater.
你对枪有多了解  笨蛋?
What do you know about guns anyway,Hoss?
它还能用
It'll work.
如果子弹是干的  那火药也是干的
If the bullets are dry,the powder's dry.
如果火药是...
If the powder's...
哦天...那到底是什么鬼东西?
What the hell is that?
是鲨鱼
It's a shark.
只是一只鲨鱼
It's only a shark.
"只是一只鲨鱼"?
"It's only a shark"?
是为了让我好过点么?
That's supposed to make me feel better?
呃  我想我知道为什么鲨鱼游到这儿来了
Well, I guess I know why the shark is hanging around.
你的肩膀
Your shoulder.
哦  好  那我马上去止血
Oh, well, I'll just stop bleeding then.
你突然好像什么都忘了
You suddenly forget what happened?
-我为什么会被击伤?  -什么?
-Why I got shot?  -What?
我是说  你连一点感激都没有么?
How about a little gratitude here?
我是说  你说句谢谢行不?
I mean, how about "Thank you"?
谢谢?  为了什么?
Thank you? For what?
是为了你想救自己?
For you trying to save your own ass?
你要我离开这个筏子?
You want me off this raft?
好吧
You got it!
我是为了要救你的孩子
I was trying to save your damn kid.
我们谈谈Walt好么  Dawson先生?
Let's talk about Walt, shall we,Mr Dawson?
当然  好的
Sure. OK.
你上次看到你儿子的确切时间是什么时候?
When was the last time you actually saw your son?
大概一年前吧
About a year ago.
实际上是14个月
It was fourteen months, actually.
-这是一个问题么?  -为什么  Dawson先生?
-Is that a question, Lizzy?  -Why is that, Mr Dawson?
为什么这么长时间没见孩子?
Why so long?
Susan因工作原因把他带去了阿姆斯特丹
Susan took him to Amsterdam for work.
你对这件事没有意见是么?
You didn't have a problem with that?
你说什么?
Excuse me?
因为现在她要去罗马但你又要申请禁令
Well, since she's now going to Rome and you're filing an injunction,
看起来和以前的有点矛盾
it just seems a little inconsistent.
矛盾...不
Incon... No.
-不  不  不  -她在引诱你
-No, no, no, no, no...  -She misleads you
-别回答  -尽管她带走了他
-Don't...  -She took him, though.
-我并没同意她走  -Michael拜托你别说了
-I didn't want her to go.    -Michael Please don't talk
你说过我无能为力的
You said there was nothing I could do.
然后你就什么也没做  是么?
And you didn't, did you?
他不会回答这个问题的
He's not gonna answer that.
那是因为他回答不出
Because there is no answer.
你最近是不是刚遭遇了车祸?
You were in an accident recently?
是的
Yeah.
你做了一些外科手术
You had several surgeries,
在一个私人医院里呆了几个星期
spent weeks in a private hospital room,
基本康复了
extensive rehabilitation.
是谁付的钱  Dawson先生?
Who paid for all that, Mr Dawson?
我并没有向你要过什么
I didn't ask you for anything.
这是不是能说明Dawson先生承认
Could the record reflect Mr Dawson acknowledged
Lloyd小姐帮他付了这些钱?
Miss Lloyd paid his bills?
Susan  告诉他们我并没有向你要过什么
Susan, tell them that I didn't ask you...
请别直接向我的委托人发话
Please don't address my client directly.
你知道Walt学会的第一个单词是什么吗 Dawson先生?
Do you know what Walt's first words were, Mr Dawson?
他学会的第一句话  你知道是什么么?
His first words.Do you know what they were?
我...不知道
I...No.
我...我当时不在场
I... I wasn't there.
你知道他最喜欢的食物么?
Do you know what his favourite food is?
-你知道...  -好了  够了  都是不必要的
-Do you...  -OK. This is unnecessary...
不知道
No.
对于一个死命要保留做父亲权力的人来说
Well, for someone who wants to retain his paternal rights so badly,
你是不是太不了解你的孩子了  Dawson先生
you don't seem to know much about your son, Mr Dawson.
我是他的父亲
I'm his father.
抱歉  能说得响点么  是说给记录员听的
I'm sorry, could you say that louder,please?  Just for the record
我是他的父亲
I'm his father.
你疯了么?
Are you crazy?
你想徒手取出子弹么?
You gonna take the bullet out with your bare hands?
你有更好的主意么?
You got a better idea?
那就呆一边儿去
Then go to hell.
你一个人是做不到的
Never gonna be able to do it by yourself.
我想我们已经分道扬镳了  Mike
I thought we parted ways.Mike
我们都被困在同样的洋流上
We're caught in the same current.
你还要说什么?
He's still talking.
拜托
Come on...
还有什么要补充的么?
You got a Band-Aid?
你是么?
Are you?
你是他么?
Are you him?
是的
Yes.
是的  我是
Yes, I am.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it.
你终于来了
You're finally here.
恩...
Well,
我来了
here I am.
她是谁?
Who's she?
她是和我一起的
She's with me.
一个雪人对另一个雪人说了什么?
What did one snowman say to the other snowman?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
把刀放下
Get rid of the knife.
你不是他
You're not him!
我们不是来伤害你的
We didn't come here to hurt you.
是么?  那你们来干什么?
Yeah? Then why did you come?
我们遭遇了坠机
We were in a plane crash.
刚刚么?
Were you now?
还是什么时候?
And when was that?
44天前
44 days ago.
44天?
44 days?
走
Move.
-你在这儿呆了多久了?  -闭嘴
-How long have you been down here?  -Shut it.
把他绑起来
Tie him up.
快点
Do it!
等等  等等  等等 你绑错人了
Wait, wait, you're tying up the wrong person.
怎么说?
How's that, brother?
绑我是毫无意义的  我不是危险人物
It's pointless to tie me up,I'm not dangerous.
但是她  她是一个逃犯
But her? She's a fugitive.
那你又是干什么的?
What does that make you, then, brother?
我是一个纸板生产公司的区域经理
I'm a regional collections manager for a cardboard manufacturer.
主要是生产盒子
Boxes, primarily.
好吧  那么  盒子先生  把她绑起来
All right then, Box Man. Tie her up.
你别想碰...
Don't you dare touch...
给我老实一点  行不?
Hey!You be a good girl, right?
-你知道你在干什么么?  -干对我们两个都好的事
-What do you think you're doing?  -What's best for all of us.
好的  把她带到这边来
Right, bring her here.
John  嘿  等等  嘿
Hey, John...Hey, wait! Hey!
-关上门   -等等
-Shut it.   -Wait!
你是在开玩笑吧  你要回去那里?
You're kiddin', right?You're going back?
是的
Yeah.
那你说的那些
What about all that stuff you said
等着看日出的话是怎么回事?
about waiting until morning and watching the sun rise?
我改变主意了
I changed my mind.
你想是怎么回事?
What do you suppose all that's about?
我猜Jack要做一些豪情壮举了
I reckon Jack's going to do something heroic.
怎么了?
What?
你总是以故意说笑来掩饰
You always try to be funny
当你不想回答一个问题的时候
when you don't want to answer a question.
"故意"说笑?
"Try" to be funny?
这是什么?
What's this?
噢  在丛林里找到的
I found it in the jungle.
-你找到的?     -是的
-You found it?    -Yeah.
当心  拿着那东西要小心点
Be careful...Be careful with it.
来来  抱着Aaron
Here, hey, take Aaron.
来吧  接住你了
Come here. There you go.
你得小心点  你知道  这是圣母玛利亚
You gotta be careful with it, you know,it's the Virgin Mary.
她是很神圣的
She's holy.
倒没发现你居然是这么虔诚的信徒
I didn't realise you were so religious.
我不是  这只是...你知道
I'm not. It's just, you know,
它迟早会派上用场的
it might come in handy.
带在身上是不错的东西
Be a nice thing to have around.
那不是因为闪光弹
It wasn't the flare.
我说了  那不是因为闪光弹
I said it wasn't the flare.
那些人这么做...
Those people that did this...
起先我以为他们是渔民或是海盗什么的
At first I thought they were fishermen or pirates or something.
然后我仔细看了他们的船
Then I got a good look at their boat.
你了解船么  Mike?
You know anything about boats, Mike?
那种船不是用来在大洋上开的
Boat like that wasn't built for the open ocean.
一点小风小浪就能让船进水
Water's coming over the side the first little squall.
航程可能也就一百多里吧
Maybe got a range of a hundred miles.
不  像那样的船应该是在一个很近的码头驶出的
Nope. A boat like that had to have left port from somewhere close.
比如说那个岛
Like the island.
法国女人说"其他人"是冲着孩子来的
French chick said the Others were coming for the kid.
我认为他们来了  Mike
I think they came, Mike.
-什么?    -他是他们想要的人
-What?    -He's the one they wanted,
我肩膀为什么会中弹
why I got a bullet in my shoulder.
那些人炸飞了我们就是因为他们想要你的孩子
Bluebeard blew us up because they wanted your kid.
-你是说这都是我的错?    -是的  这就是我要说的
-You saying this is my fault?    -Yeah. That's what I'm sayin'.
-他们是因为你才带走我的孩子的    -我们
-They took him because of you.   -We
他们当时已经驶远了
They were sailing away!
他们找到我们是因为他们在找我们  在找Walt
They found us because they were looking for us! For Walt!
你不许再叫他的名字  不许
Don't ever say his name again, ever!
你能怎么样  用水泼我?
What you gonna do? Splash me?
-听着  我知道...   -闭嘴
-Look. I know...    -Shut up!
别说了
Don't even...
你根本不知道怎么关心别人
You have no idea what it's like to care for somebody else.
你的律师呢?
Where are your lawyers?
我跟他们说了  我想和你单独谈谈
I told them I wanted to talk.Just you and me.
但如果你想让你的律师来  我能理解
But if you want yours, I understand.
不  不用了
No. It's OK.
我想你会赢
I think you're gonna win.
-什么?  -在法庭上
-Excuse me?  -In court.
我想你会有权阻止我带着Walt离开的
I think you're going to keep me from leaving the country with Walt.
但是我只是...想问你为什么
But I just have to ask you why.
-什么为什么?  -你为什么这么做?
-Why what?  -Why are you doing this?
-他是我的儿子  -从什么时候开始的  Michael?
-He's my son.  -Since when, Michael?
听着  我知道你不关心我如何好过
Look, I know you don't care about what's best for me,
但是在罗马  我在公司可以是一个资深合伙人
but in Rome I'll be a senior partner at the firm.
我可以给Walt他需要的一切
I'll be able to give Walt anything he needs.
你现在行动仍然受限Michael  你无法工作
You're still on disability, Michael.You can't work.
你的公寓快被收回了
You're about to be evicted.
你的律师是在调查我么?
Got your lawyers checking up on me?
恩  当然是的
Of course I did.
就像你的律师也在调查我一样
Just like you had your lawyers check up on me.
-大家都不是赢家  -那么住口
-Nobody's winning.  -Then stop.
Michael  你需要做的第一件事是照顾好你自己
Michael, the first thing you need to do is take care of yourself.
你得健康起来
You need to get healthy,
你得有足够的经济基础
you need to get back on your feet financially
那样你才能继续回去追求你的艺术
so you can get back to pursuing your art.
作为一个艺术家你有罕见的天份  Michael
You have rare talent as an artist,Michael.
但是你怎么才能做到这些事呢
But how are you going to do that,any of that,
这样能成为Walt生命中的一部分么?
and still be a part of Walt's life?
我会通过努力做到的
I'll do it by doing it.
抚养Walt也是我的责任
Walt is my responsibility too.
那么就放他走
Then let him go.
因为这不是关于我和你的事
Because it's not about you or me.
这是他的事
It's about him.
我不想和你打官司  Michael
I don't want to go to court, Michael.
那么就拜托你...
So please, just...
放他走吧
let him go.
飞行员说我们失去了无线电联络
The pilot said we had lost radio contact,
但是在那之前  我们已经偏离了航线近千里了
but by then we were already a thousand miles off course.
并且搜救队几周前就应该放弃搜索了
Any search teams would've given up weeks ago.
那么你正从悉尼飞往洛杉矶?
So you were travelling from Sydney to Los Angeles?
是的
Yes.
那么另外那些人还在外面?
So the world is still out there?
就我所知  是的
Yeah, as far as I know.
你能告诉我你的名字么?
Could you tell me your name?
我的名字?
My name?
我叫Desmond
My name is Desmond.
Desmond  我是John
Desmond, I'm John.
你得明白  现在真的不需要这把枪了
You should know the gun is really unnecessary.
噢  是么?
Oh yeah?
那么我应该把它交给你了  是么?
So I should just hand it over to you then, should I?
你们那儿有多少人?
How many of you are there?
呃  43个  但是有4个今天早上坐筏子出海了
43. But four sailed out this morning on a raft.
筏子?
A raft?
那个模拟日光  是因为你从来不离开么?
That simulated sunlight,is that because you never leave?
还有其他的出口么?
Is there another way out?
你们有多少人生病了?
How many of your group have gotten sick?
生病?
Sick?
生病  就是病了死了
Sick. As in ill. As in dead.
这就是为什么舱门里写着"检疫隔离"的原因么?
Is that why it says "Quarantine"on the hatch?
-回答我     -没人生病  没有人
-Answer the question!    -No one has... No one,
没有人得病
no one is sick.
起来
Get up.
走
Move.
站在这儿
Stand right there.
你知道怎么用这个么  盒子先生?
Do you know how to use this, Box Man?
-我已经20年没见过这个了  -你知道怎么用么?
-Haven't seen one of those in 20 years.  -Do you know how?
-是的  -坐下
-Yes.  -Sit.
好的  现在仔细听着
Right, now listen carefully.
我说什么你打什么  懂么
Type in exactly what I tell you.Understand?
要绝对正确  不许输错
Exactly. Nothing else.
-你听到了么?  -什么?
-Do you hear that?  -What?
你刚输了什么?
What'd you just put in?
-你刚刚输的是哪个数?  -15
-What number did you just put in?  -15.
好的  16
Right. 16...
现在按执行健
Now press "Execute. "
-会发生什么事?  -快按
-What's gonna happen?  -Just push it.
Kate
Locke
是谁?
Who the hell is that?
一定是Jack
That would be Jack.
他是谁?
Who is he?
他叫Jack
His name is Jack.
他是我们的医生
He's our doctor.
他在这儿干什么?
What's he doing here?
老实和你说吧  看到他我也觉得很惊讶
To be honest with you,I'm a little surprised to see him.
你们的医生带着枪
Your doctor has a gun, brother.
走
Move.
别出声  不然我就开枪
Make one sound and I'll shoot.
走
Move!
Jack
如果是我 我不会这么做  Jack
I wouldn't do that, Jack.
- Kate在哪儿?  -你到底...
-Where's Kate?  -What the hell did you...
滚...
Move
不然我杀了他
and I kill him.
-放下枪  -Kate在哪儿?
-Put the gun down.  -Where's Kate?
-Jack  没事的  -我说了  放下枪
-Jack, it's OK.  -I said drop it!
-Kate在哪儿?  -她没事  放下...
-Where's Kate?  -She's fine. Just put down...
我什么也不放
I'm not putting down anything...
你想他死么?  放下枪
Do you want him to die? Put it down.
这就是你所说的么  Locke?
Is this what you were talking about,Locke?
这就是你的命运么?
Is this your destiny?
-"该发生的总会发生的"    -冷静点
-"All roads lead here"?    -Calm down.
放下枪
Lower your gun,
否则我崩了他的脑袋
or I'll blow his damned head off, brother.
是你
You!
那是什么鬼东西?
What the hell is that?
筏子的一部分  浮着的竹筒
It's part of the raft,one of the pontoons.
别划了
Stop paddling.
嘿  停下
Hey, stop it!
你把绳索拉太猛了  筏子会散架的
You're putting a strain on the vines. It's going to break us up.
混蛋  你会...
Damn it, you're gonna sink us!
Sawyer
-上来    -我上来的话我们都会沉下去
-Climb up!    -I do and we both sink.
我游到竹筒那儿去
I'm going for the pontoon.
别傻了
Don't be an idiot.
你看到那个尖牙的畜牲
You see that toothy son of a bitch,
-瞄准了就开枪  知道了么    -知道了
-you aim and squeeze. Got it?  -Got it.
加油  加油  快  快
Come on! Come on, come on!
Sawyer
把手给我
Gimme your hand!
他在那儿  看见了么?
There he is. Do you see him?
抱歉我迟到了  打理东西很麻烦
I'm sorry I'm late.Packing's been a disaster
而飞机一早就飞走了
and the plane leaves first thing in the morning.
恩  没关系
Sure. No problem.
呃  嘿  打个招呼吧  Walt
Hey, do you wanna say hi, Walt?
嘿  Walt  我是...
Hi, Walt. I'm...
我是...
I'm...
嘿  呃  这是给你的
Hey, this is for you, man.
-他喜欢熊么?    -是的  呃  当然
-He like bears?    -Yes. Sure.
他只是很害羞
He's just really shy.
嘿  小伙计
Hey, little man.
噢  我想我不能这么叫你
Well, I guess I can't call you that,
我是说  因为看你已经这么大了
I mean, because look how big you are.
那么...
So,
你和我  我们将会有段时间不能见面了Walt
you and I, we're not gonna see each other for a while, Walt.
但是你会生活得很好的
But you are gonna have a great life.
我知道你的妈妈  她会
I know your mommy,she's going
好好照顾你的
to take real good care of you.
并且Brian也会...
And Brian is gonna
好好照看你的
take good care of you, too.
但是你知道么?
But you know what?
我要你知道
I just want you to know
不管你去了哪儿
that no matter where you go,
我...
I...
你的爸爸...
That your daddy...
是的  你的爸爸...他真的很爱很爱你
Yeah, your daddy,he loves you very, very much.
并且永远会的
And I always will.
永远  好么?
Always. OK?
-我很抱歉  他很...    -不   没关系
-I'm sorry, he's...    -No. It's OK.
没关系
It's OK.
嘿  给你  呃...
Hey, here.
只是  你知道...
Just, you know...
你知道  到时候让他知道是我送的  好么?
Let him know it's from me sometime, OK?
好的
OK.
再见  Michael
Goodbye, Michael.
好  再见
Yeah. Bye.
你没事吧  Mike?
You all right, Mike?
是我的错
It's my fault.
什么?
What?
我不应该把他带上筏子的
I never should have brought him on the raft.
我要把他找回来
I'm gonna get him back.
我要把我儿子找回来
I'm gonna get back my son.
看看这个
How about that?
洋流把我们带回来了
Current brought us back.
我们回来了
We're home.
Jin?
Michael  Sawyer    -Jin
Jin
其他人  其他人
Others! Others!
-什么?    -其他人  其他人
-What?    -Others! Others!
-什么?    -其他人
-What?    -Others
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====